Now that we have topologies for
现在我们有 6 个手势的拓扑图
our six signs, let's talk about phrase level sign language recognition.
我们讨论短语级别的手语识别
We have eight phrases we want to recognize.
我们想要识别 8 个短语
&gt;&gt; Actually, you mean 7 signs and 12 phrases.
— 实际上你是指 7 个手势和 12 个短语
&gt;&gt; Since we have two variants of cat we are recognizing,
— 既然我们识别到 cat 的两个变化
expanding all the possibilities leads to 12 phrases.
扩展所有可能性 形成 12 个短语
&gt;&gt; Good point.
— 说的不错
To keep things simple, let's use a strict grammar.
为了简化 我们使用严谨的语法
We will always have a pronoun followed by a verb followed by a noun.
我们这里都是代词 加上动词和名词
And we'll only recognize one phrase at a time.
我们一次只识别一个短语
&gt;&gt; So let's expand that out again to be explicit.
— 我们展开来讲解
&gt;&gt; Great.
— 非常棒
Now comes the messy part.
接下来是复杂的部分
&gt;&gt; Let's assume we have data from thad's signing that we want to recognize.
— 假设我们得到了想要识别的 Thad 手势
Here he is actually signing I need cat.
这里他用手语表示 I need cat (我需要猫)
Really, that's the phrase you came up with for us to use?
这真的是你提出来我们要用的短语吗？
&gt;&gt; Everyone should have a cat.
— 每个人都需要一只猫
&gt;&gt; Meow.
— 喵
&gt;&gt; Okay, anyway suppose looking at the delta y feature through time gives us
— 好 假设观察通过时间的 Δy 特征
this string of observations.
我们得到一系列观测
&gt;&gt; Which is about 20 samples through time.
— 约有 20 个通过时间的样本
&gt;&gt; We're going to do recognition the same way as before, but
— 我们之前采用了相同的方式进行识别
with a much bigger trellis.
但是采用较大的网格图
&gt;&gt; We have 22 states to worry about.
— 我们这里有 22 个状态
Three for each of I, WE, NEED, WANT, CAT1 and CAT2 and four for TABLE.
I WE NEED WANT CAT1 和 CAT2 各有三个状态 TABLE 有四个状态
&gt;&gt; So where can we be when t is equal to one?
— 当 t 等于 1 时 我们在哪里呢？
&gt;&gt; Well, the grammar says we have to start with I or WE.
— 语法表明我们首先从 I 或 we 开始
So we have to be in the first state, of either these two pronouns.
我们首先在第一个状态 这两个代词中的一个
&gt;&gt; Where can we be when t equals to two?
— 当 t 等于 2 时 我们在哪里呢？
Well, we could stand the current state.
我们可以维持在当前状态
We could transition into the second state of I or we.
也可以转移到 I 或 we 的第二个状态
&gt;&gt; How about t equal to three?
— t 等于 3 时呢？
&gt;&gt; It's still easy.
— 还是很简单
We can be in states one through three for I or for we.
我们可以在状态 1 也可以到 I 或 we 的状态 3
We haven't had a chance to transition out the first sign yet.
我们没有转移出第一个手势
&gt;&gt; But what happens with t equal to four?
— 不过 t 等于 4 时发生什么呢？
Once we get to t equals four, we could,
一旦 t 等于 4 至少从理论上来说
at least in theory, have transitioned to either the verbs want or need.
我们可能转移到动词 want 或 need
We are beginning to see the complexity, that will soon overtake us.
我们开始看到很快出现了复杂性
&gt;&gt; That's right, but it's not too bad yet.
— 没错 但是还没有太糟糕
At t equal to five,
当 t 等于 5 时
we have more opportunities where we can transition to need or want.
我们更有可能转移到 need 或 want
But we still can't get to the nouns yet.
但是还没到名词部分
&gt;&gt; At t equals six, we're still with the pronouns and verbs.
— t 等于 6 时 我们可能还是位于代词和动词上
&gt;&gt; But, at t equals seven, we could, possibly, transition to TABLE, or CAT1,
— 不过 t 等于 7 时 我们可能转移到 TABLE CAT1
or CAT2.
或 CAT 2
&gt;&gt; At t equals eight, we could get into the second state of the noun signs, and
— t 等于 8 时 我们会到达名词手势的第二个状态
a t equals nine, we can actually transition into the third state of
当 t 等于 9 时 我们实际上转移到名词手势的
the noun signs &gt;&gt; At t equals a ten we have the first
第三个状态 — t 等于 10 时我们首次
time we can transition back from state three to state two in table.
从状态 3 回到状态 2
This loop back complicates our trellis a little bit.
这个循环让我们网格图变得有点复杂
&gt;&gt; But it's not too bad.
— 但还不算太糟糕
We just now have this back and forth structure.
我们刚才循环回来 得到第 4 个结构
&gt;&gt; And here's the full trails for
— 这是我们从示例短语中
after we taking care of all the data from the example phrase.
处理所有数据后得到的完整网格图
&gt;&gt; Wow.
— 哇塞
And this is the simplest example we could come up with.
这是我们可以提出的最简单示例
But note here, we couldn't actually reach all this states in the end.
不过注意这里 我们实际上最后不能达到所有状态
We have to get back to the bottom states of one of the three nouns.
我们会回到三个名词中其中一个的底部状态
&gt;&gt; Yup, this trail also shows how HMM is going to take up a lot of memory.
— 没错 这个网格图也表明隐马尔可夫模型会占用大量内存
&gt;&gt; Imagine if we had a vocabulary that included all of the six thousand signs
— 假如我们有个词语 包含了美式手语中所有
in the American Sign Language, or even worse yet, all the variations of those
6000 个手语 或者是一些手语的变体
signs that give the ASL its expressiveness and speed.
可以让美式手语表达丰富 更有速度
&gt;&gt; Not to mention what would happen if we were using a real grammar?
— 如果我们使用实际语法会发生什么？
Which brings up an interesting point.
这引发了很有意思的一点
Almost all of language recognizers will have problems keeping the full trellis
几乎所有语言识别器都会在保存完整网格图
and memory.
和内存方面存在问题
&gt;&gt; And keeping all the paths updated will also be a problem.
— 维持所有路径更新也会是个问题
&gt;&gt; How will we deal with this problem?
— 怎样解决这个问题呢？
&gt;&gt; We'll use the stochastic beam search.
— 我们要使用随机定向搜索